<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wings of Tomorrow</title>
    <link>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wings of Tomorrow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Wings of Tomorrow The inspiration for Wings of Tomorrow came from a group of friends who discovered the power of mentorship during their careers as aviators in the United States Navy.
Together, they built Wings of Tomorrow to empower the next generation of aviators with the knowledge and resources they wish they had early in their careers
Our Mission: The mission of Wings of Tomorrow is to provide the next generation of aviators with the opportunity for mentorship during their careers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/faqs/</guid>
      <description>How does it work?    Aspiring mentees fill out an application form to be matched with a mentor who has experience in their desired aviation field. Once matched, the mentee will now have a wingman to help them become the best aviator they can be.   How do I volunteer?    Contact us at here and we will start the screening process!   How do I become a mentee?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our team</title>
      <link>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/team/</guid>
      <description>At Wings of Tomorrow, our leadership is composed of distinguished naval aviators and industry professionals who bring a wealth of experience, passion, and leadership to our mission of mentoring the next generation of aviation professionals.
Lieutenant Andy B. Coen Founder and CEO Andy Coen is from the small Gold Rush town of Placerville, CA. He graduated from the US Naval Academy in 2017 with a B.S. in Ocean Engineering as a Burke Scholar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch Press Release</title>
      <link>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/blog/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/blog/launch/</guid>
      <description>Hey! I&amp;rsquo;m Miguel, and I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student in the department of Civil and Environmental Engineering at Vanderbilt University. I&amp;rsquo;m also the President of the Graduate Student Body and the co-founder of Dores Divest, a campus sustainable investments campaign. I grew up sailing in Annapolis, Maryland, but am now pleased to call Nashville home.
I have a diverse work history in public service, and I&amp;rsquo;d like to continue to employ myself in the pursuit of a more equitable world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our origin story</title>
      <link>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/blog/origin-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wings-of-tomorrow.org/blog/origin-story/</guid>
      <description>Hey! I&amp;rsquo;m Miguel, and I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student in the department of Civil and Environmental Engineering at Vanderbilt University. I&amp;rsquo;m also the President of the Graduate Student Body and the co-founder of Dores Divest, a campus sustainable investments campaign. I grew up sailing in Annapolis, Maryland, but am now pleased to call Nashville home.
I have a diverse work history in public service, and I&amp;rsquo;d like to continue to employ myself in the pursuit of a more equitable world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
